Guide to the Thomas Andrew Bailey Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, 1927-1967; Series 1
  - Correspondence, R-V, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Van Alstyne, R. W., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Tansill, Charles, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, V-Z, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Wilber, Allen S., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, A-C, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Bardahl, Clarence A. - Department of History, University of Illinois, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Bemis, S. F., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Crofts, F. S., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Cottrell, E. A., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, D-H, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Dittus, C. W., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Gros, Robert R., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Hunter, C. H., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, H-L, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Hayden, Sherman S. - Foreign Policy Association, about publication of book, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Koontz, Louis K., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Lippman, Walter, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, M-R, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Mitchell, Thornton, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Notter, Harley, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Robinson, E. E., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, R-V, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Spaulding, E. Wilder, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Savelle, Max, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Tressider, Donald B. - President, Stanford University, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Van Alstyne, R. W., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, V-Z, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Ward, Stuart R., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Wright, Gordon, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, A-B, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Beale, Howard K., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Bemis, S. F., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Bowman, Isaiah - President, Johns Hopkins University, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, C, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Caughey, John, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Cottrell, E. A., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Crofts, F. S., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Cunningham, C. E. - Macmillan Company, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Curti, Merle - Department of History, University of Wisconsin, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, D, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Davies, Wallace E. - Department of History, University of Maine, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Dean, A. L., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, G-H, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Gros, Robert R., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Hunter, Charles H., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Hoover, Herbert, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, I-K, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Johnstone, William C. - School of Government, George Washington University, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Klingbert, Frank, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, L-M, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Langdon, Robert M. - Department of History, Cornell University, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Latham, H. S. - Vice President, Macmillan Company, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Lutz, Ralph H., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, N-Q, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Notter, Harley F., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, R-S, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Robinson, E. E., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Savelle, Max, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Tressider, Donald B., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Schlesinger, Arthur M. - Department of History, Harvard University, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, T-Z, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Tinsley, William W., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Van Alstyne, R. W., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Ward, Stuart R., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Wilber, Allen S., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Wish, Harvey - Department of History, Smith College, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, A-B, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Beale, Howard K., 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Bemis, S. F., 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Buck, Paul H. - Dean, Harvard University, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, C-E, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Caughey, John, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Clyde, Paul H. - Department of History, Duke University, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Cottrell, E. A., 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Crofts, F. S., 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Cuningham, Charles E. - Macmilling Company, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Earle, Edward M., 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, F-H, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Hunter, C. H., 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Holt, W. Stull, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, I-L, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Klingberg, Frank W., 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Knowland, William F. - United States Senator, California, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Lanning, John Tate, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, M-R, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Merk, Frederick - Department of History, Harvard University, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Nevins, Allan, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Ragatz, Lowell, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Robinson, E. E., 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, H-I, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Holt, W. Stull, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Hill, H. W. - National War College - where Bailey taught for six months, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Gruenther, Alfred M. - National War College, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Hicks, John D. - Department of History, UC Berkeley, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, S-Z, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Savelle, Max, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Spaulding, E. Wilder, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Strevey, Tracy E. - Chairman, Department of History, Northwestern University, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Tressider, Donald B., 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Van Alstyne, R. W., 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Wilber, Allen S., 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Winther, O. O., 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Wright, Gordon, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, A-B, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Bemis, S. F., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Bradley, Harold W., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, C, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Cuningham, Charles E. - Managing Editor, Macmillan Company, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Caughey, John, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, C-H, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Crofts, F. S., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Fisher, H. H., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Hoskins, Halford L. - Director, School of Advanced International Studies, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, K-M, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Knowland, William F., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Littler, Robert, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, M-R, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Nevins, Allan, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Robinson, E. E., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, R-S, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Spindler, Arno, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Spaulding, E. Wilder, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Spinks, Charles N., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, S-Z, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Savelle, Max, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Tansill, Charles C., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Wilber, Allen S., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Wright, Gordon, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, A-B, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Arbuckle, Ernest C., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Bradley, Harold W., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, B-C, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Curti, Merle, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Cuningham, Charles E., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Caughey, John, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, C-F, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - De Conde, Alexander - Department of History, Whittier College, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Evans, Luther B. - Librarian of Congress, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Earle, Edward M., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Fisher, H. H., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, F-H, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Gros, Robert R., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Hunter, Charles H., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Hicks, John D., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, K-M, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Latham, H. S. - Macmillan Company, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Klingberg, Frank J., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, M-R, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Nevins, Allan, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Robinson, E. E., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Rothwell, Easton - Hoover Library, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, R-Z, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Spindler, Arno, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Savage, Carlton, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Wilber, Allen S., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Wish, Harvey, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Wilbur, Allen S., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, A-B, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, Charles D., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Bemis, S. F., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Billington, Ray A. - Northwestern University, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, B-D, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Dyer, Brainerd - Department of History, UCLA, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Beale, Howard K., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Cuningham, Charles E., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Caughey, John W., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, D-H, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Downey, Sheriden - United States Senator, California, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Evans, Luther H., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Earle, Edward Mead, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Hicks, J. D., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, H-K, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Hunter, Charles H., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Harrington, Fred H. - Department of History, University of Wisconsin, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, K-L, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Leebrick, K. C., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Latham, H. S. - Vice Presidence, Macmillan Company, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Knowland, William F., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Knopt, Alfred A. - publishers, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Klingberg, Frank W., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, M-P, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Owen, David - American Historical Association, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Nevins, Allan, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, R-S, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Rappaport, Armin - Department of History, UC Berkeley, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Savelle, Max, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Spindler, Arno, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, T-W, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Van Alstyne, R. W. - Department of History, USC, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Van Ness, Carl - Editor, Appleton-Century-Crofts, Inc., publishers, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Wilber, Allen S., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, W-Z, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Whitaker, Douglas M. - Dean of Graduate Studies, Stanford, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Winther, O. O., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, A-D, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Bemis, S. T., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Billington, Ray A., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Caughey, John, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, D-H, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Faust, Clarence - Dean, School of Humanities and Sciences, Stanford, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Earle, Edward Mead, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, H-M, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Holt, W. Stull, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Lutz, Ralph H., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Merk, Frederick, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, M-S, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Nevins, Allan, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Robinson, E. E., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Rappaport, Armin, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Schlesinger, Arthur M., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, S-Z, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Tanhan, George K. - California Institute of Technology, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Wilber, Allen S., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Wright, Gordon, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, A-F, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Caughey, John, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, F-K, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Hunter, Charles H., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Handlin, Oscar - Department of History, Harvard University, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Littler, Robert C., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, L-S, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Nevins, Allan, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Rappaport, Armin, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Robinson, E. E., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, S-Z, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Tanham, George K., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Wish, Harvey, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Wilber, Allen S., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, A-C, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Beale, Howard K., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Clyde, Paul C. - about moving to Duke University, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, C-L, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Hunter, Charles H., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Guerrant, Edward O., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Hicks, J. D., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, L-Z, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Nevins, Allen, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Robinson, E. E., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Rappaport, Armin, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Wilber, Allen S., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, A-C, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Beale, Howard K., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Barker, Charles A. - Department of History, Johns Hopkins University, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Creer, Leland H. - Department of History, University of Utah, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, C-F, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Clyde, Paul C., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Davies, Wallace E., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Dyer, Brainerd, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, F-H, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Guerrant, Edward O., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Gates, Paul W. - Department of History, Cornell University, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Gray, Wood - Department of History, George Washington University, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, H-M, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Howe, George F., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Jensen, Merrill - Department of History, University of Wyoming, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Leopold, Richard W., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, M-Q, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Merk, Frederick, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - O'Connor, Raymond G., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Quint, Howard H., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, R-S, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Rappaport, Armin, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, S-Z, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Sydnor, Charles S. - Department of History, Duke University, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Savelle, Max - Department of History, University of Washington, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Wilber, Allen S., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, A-J, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Beale, Howard K., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Arbuckle, Ernest C., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Clyde, Paul C., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Guerrant, Edward O., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, J-Z, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Knowland, William F., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Perkins, Dexter, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Savelle, Max, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Wilbur, Allen S., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, A-F, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Barnet, Vaughn D., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Clyde, Paul H., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, F-L, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Holt, W. Stull, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Hicks, J. D., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Leopold, Richard W., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, K-R, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Knowland, William F., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - O'Connor, Raymond G., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Ragland, James - Department of History, Long Beach State College, California, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Robinson, E. E., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, R-Z, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Rappaport, Armin, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Wilber, Allen S., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, A-C, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Arbuckle, Ernest C., 1956 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Beale, Howard K., 1956 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, C-H, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Curti, Merle, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, H-L, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Hicks, J. D., 1956 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Hunter, Charles H., 1956 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Holt, W. Stull, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Knowland, William F., 1956 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1956 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Kuchel, Thomas H., 1956 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Lutz, Ralph, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, M-S, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Rappaport, Armin, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Robinson, E. E., 1956 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Savelle, Max, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, T-W, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Wilber, Allen S., 1956 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Wright, Gordon, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, W-Z, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Younger, Edward - Department of History, University of Virginia, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, A-Z, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Langdon, Robert M., 1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Quint, Howard H., 1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Ragland, James, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Rhinelander, Philip H., 1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Younger, Edward, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, A-Z, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Clyde, Paul H., 1958 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Langdon, Robert M., 1958 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Leopold, Richard W., 1958 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Quint, Howard H., 1958 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Rhinelander, Philip H., 1958 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, A-Z, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Dyer, Brainerd, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Fong, Hiram L. - United States Senator, Hawaii, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Nevins, Allan, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Robinson, E. E., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Rappaport, Armin, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, A-D, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Caughey, John W., 1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Clyde, Paul H., 1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, D-P, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Holt, W. Stull, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Potter, David, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Perkins, Dexter, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, P-Z, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Ragland, James, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Rappaport, Armin, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Wright, Gordon, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, A-Z, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Clyde, Paul H., 1961 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - O'Connor, Raymond G., 1961 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Ragland, James, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, D. C. Heath anad Company, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Edel, Dr. Marie - College Department, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Walden, John R., 1961 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, A-Z, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Littler, Robert, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - O'Connor, Raymond G., 1962 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, D. C. Heath and Company, 1962 January - May (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Walden, John R., 1962 January - May (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Edel, Marie, 1962 January - May (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, D. C. Heath and Company, 1962 May - July (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Edel, Marie, 1962 May - July (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Walden, John R., 1962 May - July (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Sortwell, Daniel R., 1962 May - July (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, D. C. Heath and Company, 1962 July-December (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Sortwell, Daniel R., 1962 July-December (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Walden, John R., 1962 July-December (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, A-H, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Dee, Ivan R. - Managing Editor, Quadrangle Book, Inc., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, H-R, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Hicks, John D., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Kuchel, Thomas H., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Nevins, Allan, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - O'Connor, Raymond G., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Ragland, James T., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, R-Z, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Schlesinger, Jr., Arthur, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, D. C. Heath and Company, 1963 January-May (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Sortwell, Daniel, 1963 January-May (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Walden, John R., 1963 January-May (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, D. C. Heath and Company, 1963 May-December (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Sortwell, Daniel, 1963 May-December (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, A-D, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Caughey, John, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Campbell, W. Glenn - Director, Hoover Institute, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Dee, Ivan, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, D-H, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Hatfield, Mark O. - Governor of Oregon, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, H-P, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Lutz, Ralph, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - O'Connor, Raymond G., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, P-Z, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Ragland, James, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Rappaport, Armin, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Russell, Richard B. - United States Senator, Georgia, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, D. C. Heath and Company, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Quick, E. B., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Sortwell, Daniel, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, A-C, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Burton, Jack K. - Editor, Appleton-Century-Crofts Company, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, C-G, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - De Conde, Alex, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Friedal, Frank - Department of History, Harvard University, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, G-L, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Hepburn, Charles - Department of History, Texas A & M University, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 28)